LiZA did?
Yeah. She showed a strong response.
More than any we've ever seen.
I see.
So the time is almost upon us, then.
The Captured Sleeping Beauty
The sea!
Hey, Reitia!
Nii-san!
What do you think of this swimsuit?
Do we look good in these?
Yeah, I think so.
We spent a lot of time
picking them out yesterday.
Sorry, Miharu-san. I guess you got
dragged into coming along with this.
No, not at all.
I'm happy I got to come with you today.
Hey, what are you looking at?
S-Sakura!
Hey!
You're too close! Get off!
Take care of that!
Let's swim, Hayato-kun!
Hey!
Wait!
Stop it!
If only I could dress like a girl
when everyone's around...
Everyone seems to be
enjoying themselves, huh?
It was worth it to bring them here.
I think it'll be hard for you to swim,
but get some relaxation.
And what've you got
your tits hanging out for?
Are you out to seduce Hayato, too?
Wh-What are you talking about?
How rude, Emile Crossfode!
Hmph.
Now you've done it!
Wait!
Hey, you getting hungry?
I made lunch.
Disgusting.
What?
The way you keep clinging to Hayato.
And you joined the Little Garden
because you're after Hayato, right?
That's right. I've decided to be his
personal idol when I'm not performing.
I refuse to accept that!
And what about you? Are you
really just friends with him?
Or are you...
D-Does she know I'm a girl?
Or are you into boys?
Everybody's talking about it.
Saying how it's fishy that you two are
all over each other, even though you're guys.
Oh, that?
Hayato and I are close because
we used to be together in Gudenburg.
You, too?
Yup.
We were childhood friends.
Then I'm also...
No, not really.
I heard that you were
only together for a day.
We're still childhood friends!
I've been with my brother since I was born.
So maybe I'm his biggest childhood friend!
Thanks for the food, Sakura.
Did you like it?
Yes, it was great.
Yeah, it wasn't bad, I guess.
Hayato! Emile!
What say we work off
the calories with a game?
Sure, I'm in!
You can do it, Hayato-kun!
Good luck!
Here I go!
Hey, are you allowed to use Energy?
Is that a problem?
Then I'll use Energy, too!
U-Um... Claire-sama...
Would you be kind enough to
let me rub some on the front, too?
No, I'll do that.
Here, Claire-sama.
No!
This is my job!
Claire-sama, let me do your front.
No, leave it to me!
No, me!
Me!
I'm fine!
Here I go!
Reitia #1 Attack!
Not so fast!
Hayato?
Hey, Hayato-kun!
What are you doing?
Wh-What?
The Warslarn Inc. Crest?
Judar-oniisama.
Is that...
...the CEO of Warslarn?
Hello. It's been so long, Claire.
That swimsuit looks great on you.
Spare me the flattery.
That was quite the entrance, by the way.
What brings you all the way out here?
I wanted to see you
as soon as I possibly could.
And I thought I would see these brave
future soldiers of Warslarn in person.
So you're Kisaragi Hayato-kun, right?
Yes.
You surpassed my sister's response values
before you even joined.
You're the Little Garden's rising star.
And the holder of the divine blood.
Oh, just talking to myself.
Don't worry about it.
And you're Emili...
No, Emile Crossfode, yes?
Hello.
I'm told the rest of you
all have bright futures, as well.
I expect great things.
All right, Claire.
I'll take you back to the
Little Garden in my helicopter.
Come with me.
It seems something's up.
Claire-sama.
No need to worry.
What was with them?
Yeah...
The Student Council President?
She says come to the Student
Council Room immediately.
An anti-Savage cleanup operation?
Yes.
This operation will be performed
under the guidance of
the UN's joint operations task force,
the Peacekeeping Army.
So Little Garden is sending
members from the Selections.
Um, why were we called here, too?
You're going to officially
join the Selections,
and participate in this operation!
We did, Fritz!
We're in the Selections!
Yup. Let's do our best.
Kisaragi Hayato-kun?
Can I help you?
I wanted to have a little chat.
May I have a moment of your time?
But...
Okay, Fritz! Let's train!
All right. I'll go with you.
Hayato?
Um...
Hayato-kun?
Y-Yes?
Do you know what the power
source of Little Garden is?
Um...
A nuclear fusion reactor, right?
Only on paper.
The power source for this
massive academy city ship,
the power source for all of our research...
Little Garden requires
massive amounts of energy.
More than you can get out
of a fusion reactor.
So what is it that
really powers Little Garden?
This is the answer.
Just like Sleeping Beauty
in the fairy tale, isn't she?
She is the power source of Little Garden,
and its supreme commander.
LiZA.
This is LiZA?
Yes.
And the first Slayer and Variant
created by mankind.
Liza Harvey.
Harvey?
My sister, and Claire's.
Brother!
President!
Why did you bring Kisaragi Hayato here?
Oh, my.
I'm sure if Liza woke up and saw
you pointed that at me,
she'd be very shocked.
She'd say you've turned
into quite the tomboy.
Answer my question!
I'm certain that in the future,
he's going to be one of
Warslarn's top Slayers.
So he should know that there's something in
Little Garden that needs to be protected at all costs.
Something that could change the
very power balance of the world.
And who better than myself to tell him?
Oh, my.
Would you please not call my sister a thing?
I'm sorry.
But that's not the only reason
I brought him here.
He has the divine blood.
He might able to awaken Liza.
What do you mean?
Hayato-kun,
it's time for you to awaken Sleeping Beauty
from her eternal slumber.
Now, give her a wake-up kiss.
K-Kiss?
What are you talking about?
It was a joke.
The kiss is our method of last resort.
For now, just touch the capsule
and release your energy.
Try it.
Liza!
Unfortunately,
it seems that wasn't enough to wake her up.
I'm in a hurry.
As long as that woman's alive,
she may come after Liza.
Vitaly Tynyanov is her name.
Vitaly?
She and I have a past.
I need to capture her.
That's why I want to have a talk
with her servants, the Hunters.
Then this cleanup operation...
I'm done talking.
Brother!
Why not have a nice long chat with
Hayato-kun in front of your sister?
What do you mean?
If a talented Slayer were
to join the Harvey family,
that would make me very happy.
What do you think, Hayato-kun?
Judar, what are you saying?
It was just a joke.
I didn't expect you to react so strongly.
I'll be on my way, then.
You're not asking anything, huh?
You didn't look like you wanted me to ask.
I'll tell you when it's time.
And...
Keep what you heard and saw there a secret.
That is an order.
Got it?
Yeah.
I'll go over the plan once more.
This is a map of the mountains near
Tian Quan City in the Empire of Qin.
We estimate that there are
around 50 Savages in this area.
Our base camp is in Tian Quan City.
That's where Xuemei was born.
If there's something you don't understand,
ask her. She's our guide.
I-I'll be happy to help!
And there's a chance those three
will appear during this mission.
One of the reasons you were
chosen for this mission
was because you've fought them before.
Judar-sama believes it'll be easier to deal
with them if you know about them.
Then LiZA didn't pick these members?
Correct.
It was Judar-sama who proposed
this clean-up operation to the UN.
We were told about this,
but I guess this really is a big mission.
I'm getting excited!
Hey, it's a little too early to
start getting fired up, right?
The fight's tomorrow!
I know!
Don't put your hand on my head!
We're going, everyone.
Emilia-sama!
What was that?
Princess Emilia!
I missed you, Emilia-sama!
N-No!
Y-You've got the wrong person!
You can dress like a man,
but you can't fool me!
I'm sure that you're Princess Em...
Shut up!
Princess?
I was sure if I came here,
I could meet you, Princess!
Stop calling me that!
What's with this princess thing?
What's with you?
Me?
I'm Emile's classmate, Kisaragi Hayato.
Claudia, when you ask someone their name,
you're supposed to give your own name first.
I'm Claudia Loetty.
I'm from Gudenburg, part of
the Federation of Britannia,
and a Britannia Unified Army Slayer.
And Emilia-sama's childhood friend.
That's all!
I see. Nice to meet...
Emilia-sama, please come back to Gudenburg!
I knew that was it.
Everyone's waiting for the return of
Emilia Gudenburg, the hidden princess!
Shh!
Th-The hidden princess?
What's that?
It's, well...
Emile?
Hayato, there's actually a secret
I've been keeping for ten years.
The name I gave you ten years ago,
Emilia Hermit, is a fake name.
My real name is Emilia Gudenburg.
In other words, a princess
of the Gudenburg royal family.
A princess?
Sorry for keeping it a secret.
And I may be a princess,
but I'm just the third in line.
U-Um...
Emilia-sama, when this mission is over,
let's go back to Gudenburg together!
I can't do that.
I've decided that I'm never
going back to Gudenburg.
But... do you know how lonely
I've been without you?
I love you!
Claudia!
Please, come back for me!
Sorry, but...
I love Hayato more than
you love me!
So I won't go back to Gudenburg!
In other words,
everything is that man's fault.
Is that correct?
Kisaragi Hayato!
Have a duel with me,
and the winner gets Emilia-sama!
How did this happen?
If I win, I'm taking Emilia-sama
back to Gudenburg.
If, by some miracle, you win,
she stays on the Little Garden.
Got it?
But we've got the mission tomorrow,
and this dojo is also...
Xuemei-neesama told me the situation.
This is our dojo.
Feel free to use it.
Hayato, win for me!
Fine.
It's a one-round fight.
First to hit the other wins.
No using Hundreds, of course,
and no using Sense Energy!
Yeah.
You're fighting with a
weak weapon like that?
No complaining later.
I trained in kendo with this in Yamato.
It'll be fine!
Then I won't hold back!
Okay, begin!
Wh—
That was just a little test!
Watch me, Emilia-sama!
I'll beat the living shit out of him—
You're so cool, Hayato!
E-Emilia-sama!
You're going to pay for
seducing Emilia-sama!
I did not!
No more talking!
Prepare to die!
You playboy! Manwhore!
That's not what's going on!
I knew I couldn't let
Emilia-sama stay with you!
I will win this fight, no matter what!
Take this, asshole!
The match is over!
You okay?
You won!
That's my Hayato!
Hey, Emile!
N-Not bad...
Kisaragi Hayato.
Okay, that's enough practice.
The duel is a three-round fight.
Nobody said that.
Okay, best of five?
Not happening.
Then we can play rock, paper, scissors.
Hey, Emile, would it hurt
that much to go home for a little?
Never!
So give up on taking me home with you, okay?
No!
I'm never giving up!
I'll get you for this, Kisaragi Hayato.
Sheesh...
I still can't believe you're
a princess, though.
Come on, forget that.
I'm hungry.
Look, fried Xiaolongbao!
You're so silly.
Night at the Lake